

GET TO KNOW ME

I am 24 years old, I am an ambitious, purposeful and determined guy. My goal is to become a senior in the frontend development industry. I am not afraid of difficulties, I always go to my goal, I quickly adapt to any task and I am a perfectionist at heart. I am fond of intellectual games (chess, corners, dots, etc.), I love evening walks and sports, I spend my leisure time either watching movies or studying documentation, and of course I love programming and JavaScript. In conclusion, I want to say that I will achieve my goal and become a senior frontend developer and I hope that it is with you that I will go through this thorny path!:)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance (08.2019 - present)

Frontend Developer.

Layout of websites in HTML, CSS, JS and editing of the existing layout.

Sicom Company

Frontend Developer (01.2020 - present).

Development, support and modernization of company projects. Writing Javascript plugins.

Team Lead (05.2020 - present).

Project and team management.

GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Number: +38 (050) 010 33 16 Email: airkross123@gmail.com Github: github.com/airkross

VK: /devilbraz

<u>Instagram: /airkr_23</u>

Telegram: @Ruslan Guseinov

TECHNOLOGIES

CODING:

HTML5 CSS3 SASS/SCSS FlexBox BEM BootStrap4
Adaptive/Responsive/Semantic JavaScript EcmaScript6+
JQuery AJAX VueJS vue-router vuex Vuelidate NuxtJS
Webpack Gulp git git-flow npm Docker

DESIGN:

Figma Avocode

PROJECT MANAGEMENT:
Redmine Yandex Traker Flowlu

EDUCATION

Donetsk National Technical University (Undergraduate, 09.2014 - 07.2018)

FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY Specialty «Information management systems»

Don State Technical University (Magistracy, 09.2018 - 12.2020)

FACULTY OF MASTER'S DEGREE
Specialty «Computing systems and information security»

LANGUAGES

<u>Russian - 10 / 10</u> <u>Ukrainian - 10 / 10</u>

English - 5 / 10